Guide to the Robert Averill Walker Papers SC0546
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Original Accession, Accession ARCH-1998-097
  - International Studies Committee, Ad Hoc Committee Charter, 1967 March (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Education and World Affairs, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committee of Fifteen, Judicial System (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Committee of Fifteen, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committee of Fifteen, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Accreditation Reports, 1965/1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Committees (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Council (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Corson Report (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Academic Council, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A. A. U. P. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chancellor (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Committee Assignments and Membership (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Judicial Procedures, Including CUE, SCLC, and SJC, 1963-1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Semester vs. Quarter general (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Overseas Programs - misc., 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Division (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Humanities & Sciences on General Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Humanities & Sciences on Overseas Campuses, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Humanities & Sciences general (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Invitations, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Provost's Office Budget - General Studies, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Provost's Office general, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reports, General Studies & Overseas Campuses (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Campuses, Publicity (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Campuses, Statistics (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Sub-Committee, Martindale Report (Ad Hoc Comm. On OC) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - GSC, Maccoby Study re Overseas Campuses, Spring 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - African Overseas Study Program, recommendations and report (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - African Overseas Study Program, general (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - African Overseas Study Program, notes on visit (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - African Overseas Study Program, univ. contacts (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - African Overseas Study Program, C.S.I.S. contacts (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - African Overseas Study Program, exploratory trip (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ghana (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Sierra Leone (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Nigeria (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Liberia (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bunzel, John, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Brody, Richard, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - La Porte, T., correspondence (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Laing, James, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cotter, C., correspondence (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rogow, A., correspondence (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Travis, Martin, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Horn, Robert, correspondence (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Shapiro, M., correspondence (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Academic Senate Committee Structure of the University (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Academic Senate Charter, 1968 April 11 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Academic Senate Membership (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Academic Senate charges and documents, 1969 - 1971 June (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Academic Senate Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Academic Senate Reports, 1970/1971 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Academic Senate Reports, 1969/1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Academic Senate Reports, 1968/1969 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Academic Senate General, 1968 June - 1969 December (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Academic Council General (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Academic Council Faculty Self-Discipline (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Academic Council correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1971 September - 1974 September (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Academic Council Minutes and memos, 1968 September - 1971 March (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1967 June - 1968 September (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1965 Sept. - 1967 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Academic Council, pass-fail option, 1966 June and 1969 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Committee for International Studies, documents, 1957 January - 1963 November (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Committee for International Studies, documents, 1964 February - 1966 October (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee for International Studies, documents, 1967 January - 1969 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Committee for International Studies, documents, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee on General Studies, documents, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1961 January - May (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1961 June - December (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1962 January - March (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1962 April - May (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1962 June - December (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1963 January - March (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1963 April - May (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Committee for General Studies, index to minutes of 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1963 September - December (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1964 February - March (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1964 April - May (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1964 August - December (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1965 January - February (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1965 April - June (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1965 October - 1966 January (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1966 February - June (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1966 October - December (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1967 January - March (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1967 June (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1967 October - December (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1968 January - April (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Committee for General Studies, documents, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Committee for General Studies, agenda and index to minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Committee for General Studies, index to minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Committee for General Studies, index to minutes, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Committee for General Studies, minutes, 1968 - 1969 April (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Committee for General Studies, index to minutes, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, minutes, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, minutes, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, index to minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1966 December 6 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1967 February - May (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1967 June - October (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1968 February - March (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1968 April - November (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1969 January - February (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses, meeting, 1969 April - June (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Photograph Albums on Overseas Campuses, 1960-66 (Box 10)
    Scope and Contents note
    France-Italy-Germany-Britain: student groups, usually posed by their plane
  - Stanford in France, Tours, 1960-70: buildings, student groups, outings, dedication ceremony (red binder) (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Austria, 1967-68: faci lities, buildings, student groups (brown binder) (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Italy, 1962-69: mostly people and events (black binder) (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1960-68: buildings, classes, outings, etc. (reddish brown binder) (Box 10)
  - "Stanford in Italy, Villa S. Paolo, Florence", n.d.: classes, events, some facilities (leather cover, stamped gold title) (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Florence: 1960 dedication and students (green binder) (Box 10)
  - Directors Conference at Stanford in Germany, January 1965 (red binder) (Box 11)
  - Intercollegiate Center for Classical Studies in Rome, n.d. (red binder) (Box 11)
  - Various student groups off to overseas campuses (green binder) (Box 11)
  - Seminar in American Studies, Japan (blue corduroy binder) (Box 11)
  - Stanford in Italy 1960-73: student groups, classes, events (brown "magnetic" type), 1960-1973 (Box 11)
  - Folders of loose photographs (Box 11)
  - Carousel of slides (Box 11)
  - Framed photographs of overseas campuses (Box 12)
  - Slides of Austria, Italy, Germany (Box 13)
    - Austria, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Britain, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - France, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Germany, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Italy, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Notes (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Slides of France, Austria, Spain, and miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - Austria, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Austria, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Austria, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Austria - Field Trip, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Austria - Innsbruck, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Austria - Vienna, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Belgium, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Britain, 1965, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Departures, 1965-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - France, 1955, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - France, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - France, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - France - Caen, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - France - Field Trip, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - France - Le Mans, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - France - Omaha Beach, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - France - Paris, 1955-1964 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - France - Versailles, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Germany - Beutelsbach, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Spain, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Spain - Madrid, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Spain - Salamanca, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Slides of France and miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Slides of Britain and France (Box 16)
  - Audio tapes (in mailing packages): 2 recorded and mailed from Tours, 1970, and Vienna, 1971; 6 unmailed, possibly blank tapes (Box 17)
  - Dick Walker, letters (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dick Walker, financial and misc. papers (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dick Walker, financial papers and overseas letters, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dick and Jerry Walker, Jr. And Sr. High School grades (1 of2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dick and Jerry Walker, Jr. And Sr. High School grades (2 of2) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Jerry Walker at Stanford (1 of2) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jerry Walker at Stanford (2 of2) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Committee on General Studies [binder of various documents] (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Preliminary Report of Committee on Committees, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Stanford study of education (raw data) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: Stanford views; pres. of Mills College (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Committee on International Studies, minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Proposals to National Science Foundation, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Degrees and 3yr Programs (correspondence, minutes, memos), 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Historical Society, minutes, 1995 January 18 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Pan American menu/welcome: S.U. flight to Stuttgart, 1961 January 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Overseas Committee, miscellaneous items (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Robert Horn Committee, letter, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Clippings re educational issues, photocopied, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Political Science 110, final examination, Winter 1950 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous certificates (Box 19)
  - Photographs (2) (Box 19)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1998-114
  - International Studies Committee - reports, background reading, memoranda, work papers [occassional minutes], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - International Studies Committee - reports, background reading, memoranda, work papers [occassional minutes], 1958 January - April (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - International Studies Committee - reports, background reading, memoranda, work papers [occassional minutes], 1958 March - April (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - International Studies Committee - reports, background reading, memoranda, work papers [occassional minutes], 1958 June - 1959 January (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - International Studies Committee - Conflict Study Seminar, 1959 (agenda and readings) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on East Asian Research, minutes, 1959 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Study of Undergraduate Education, part 1 (minutes, memoranda, reports, working papers 250 - 261) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Study of Undergraduate Education, part 2 (minutes, memoranda, reports, working papers 230 - 249) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Study of Undergraduate Education, part 3 (minutes, memoranda, reports, working papers 201 - 228) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Study of Undergraduate Education, part 4 (minutes, memoranda, reports, working papers 119 - 124) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Study of Undergraduate Education, part 5 (minutes, memoranda, reports) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, minutes, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, minutes, 1967 - 1968 June (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, minutes, 1968 October - 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Committee on University Policy, minutes and proceedings, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committee on University Policy, minutes and proceedings, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Committee on University Policy, minutes and proceedings, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committee on University Policy, minutes and proceedings, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee on University Policy, index to minutes and miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, minutes, 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, minutes, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, minutes, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, index to minutes, 1950-57 (copy 1), 1950-1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, index to minutes, 1950-57 (copy 2), 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, index to minutes, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Educ. Digest #342-A-232, #344-A-234, Nov. 1972 (copied clippings and articles), 1972 November (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1998-127
  - Parliamentary Law, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Committee on International relations and Area Studies, report, 1954 (Box 1)
  - A Discussion of Stanford's Needs and Opportunities, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
  - News clippings--Campus Report, Stanford Daily, 1973 Jan 4 (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Survey of the Behavioral Sciences, draft report, 1954 (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Survey of the Behavioral Sciences, report, 1954 Jul (Box 1)